# Hannah Melton

602.600.7635 | Phoenix, AZ 85018 | hannah.melton63@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/hannah-melton | github.com/hannahm63 | hannahm63.github.io

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with a background in Marketing. Self-starting team player known for problem solving and logistic abilities. Experience analyzing business and team needs to recommend and implement software and other solutions. Development and marketing experience in the build-out and launch of new websites.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

React	MySQL	HTML 5
Node.js	Sequelize	CSS 3
Express	MongoDB	JavaScript
Git	Mongoose	jQuery

## **PROJECTS**

## Casino S.H.I.C.

casino-shic.herokuapp.com

Free online casino games built on React, Node, MongoDB, Auth0, and Socket.io. Users can play games, earn points, and chat with each other.

## GameOn

game-on3.herokuapp.com

Game review site built with HTML, CSS animation, a third-party API, and SQL. Users can look up information about games and leave reviews.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Marketing Project Manager**

TheBestIRS, Phoenix, AZ - June 2018-Present

- o Learned new software and created production-ready video for shows in a very limited timeframe
- o Conducted market and competitor research, suggested and implemented changes to social strategy
- o Coded email templates compatible with all major email providers for use via Salesforce and ActOn
- o Worked with and set up Google Analytics and SEO and assisted with design and launch of new website

# Marketing Assistant

# Attitude Is Free, Phoenix, AZ - Aug. 2018-Dec. 2019

- o Researched and implemented inventory management application increasing efficiency and organization
- o Managed projects and events, gathering and communicating data about processes and progress
- o Exceeded expectations in fast-paced e-commerce environment with frequent changes in deadlines and priorities
- o Assisted with the launch of new website on Shopify

# Manager of Inventory Control

Hi Health, Scottsdale, AZ - Nov. 2016-May 2018

- o Built and nurtured positive relationships with vendors
- o Analyzed the most cost effective purchase orders based on sales projections
- o Learned to use and debug issues within Microsoft Access database and large Excel workbooks with Macros and utilize FTP servers to send and receive files from vendors

## **EDUCATION**

Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development University of Arizona, 2019-2020

Coursework completed towards a Bachelor of Science in Biology Research Mississippi College, 2012-2015

Relevant coursework: Intro to Computer Science, Graduate Research Project on reptile behavior gathering and analyzing data